<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="help_main_text">
        All numbers are clickable.\n
        \n
        Single click provides expected action:\n
        - main clock: start/pause;\n
        - shot clock: start new or switch to short possession (if enabled in settings);\n
        - score: increase value by 2;\n
        - period: set new period and set to default corresponding values;\n
        - fouls and timeouts: increase value by one.\n
        \n
        Long press:\n
        - main and shot clock: allows to change current value;\n
        - other number elements: will set zero state;\n
        - team names: set new team name.\n
        * Long click actions work only if main time on pause.
    </string>

    <string name="help_side_panels_enable">Enable side panels</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_intro">Use side panels to keep statistics of players</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_open">Click on bottom button of left or right side panel at the main screen to open it</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_add_one">Add one player</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_add_multi">Automatically add players. (Restoring data on long press)</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_select">Select active players: click toggle button, choose players from table above and click again to apply</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_close">Close panel (also you can tap outside the panel)</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_clear">Clear panel (shows dialog with two options: delete all players or clear points and fouls)</string>
    <string name="description_open_panel">Open panel</string>

    <string name="help_panels_text_game">
        After adding the players and choice of active players each button on the main screen will be assigned to the relevant player.\n
        When changing score or foul click on player button to apply the action to the player.\n
        Substitution active players can be either through the panel, or after long pressing on the button of the player.\n
        \n
        * Currently, automatic data recovery players panels not working. So you have to do it manually by long pressing the button automatic adding multiple players.
    </string>

    <string name="appupdate_title">Update info</string>
    <string name="appupdate_info">
        v.2.2:\n
            - portrait orientation;\n
            - possession arrows;\n
            - fix the bug of non-closing panels.\n
        v.2.1:\n
            - switch sides.\n
        v.2.0:\n
            - new help;\n
            - players panels (see help).\n
    </string>

    <string-array name="help_activity_values">
        <item>Main interface</item>
        <item>Side panels</item>
        <item>Basketball rules in app</item>
        <item>About update</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
