<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="help_activity_values">
        <item>Main interface</item>
        <item>Side panels</item>
        <item>Teams profiles</item>
        <item>Basketball rules in app</item>
        <item>Privacy policy</item>
        <item>About update</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="help_main_text">
        All numbers are clickable.\n
        \n
        Single click provides expected action:\n
        - main clock: start/pause;\n
        * in \"Streetball\" mode when main time ends main clock switches to direct timer;\n
        - shot clock: start new or switch to short possession (if enabled in settings);\n
        - score: increase value by 2 (by 1 for streetball);\n
        - period: set new period and set to default corresponding values;\n
        - fouls and timeouts: increase value by one.\n
        \n
        Long press:\n
        - main and shot clock: allows to change current value;\n
        - other number elements: will set zero state;\n
        - team names: set new team name.\n
        * Long click actions work only if main time on pause.\n
        \n
        Back button:\n
        if \"Play-by-play history\" setting is selected to keep, then canceled one last action of the press (excluding the time), otherwise, after double-clicking the application closing occurs.
    </string>

    <string name="help_profiles_text">
        You can save teams and players.\n
        \n
        Go to the Teams section to manage teams.\n
        New team can be added in two ways:\n
        1. in Teams section;\n
        2. after the game when you start a new game.\n
        \n
        In Teams section you can look at the team stats and manage players.\n
        \n
        The choice of the team for a game is possible in three ways:\n
        1. select when starting new game;\n
        2. by long pressing team name;\n
        3. from the side panels by group adding.\n
        \n
        If there are to many players in team for the current game type (12 for basketball and 4 for streetball) a dialog for selecting players for the game will be displayed.\n
        If there are to few players in team for the current game type a warning dialog will be displayed but you can start the game.\n
    </string>

    <string name="help_privacy_text">
        Privacy policy\n
        \n
        Current version https://www.dropbox.com/s/nugu370maifwb10/BasketballScoreboard.txt?dl=0\n
        \n
        Last modified: March 4, 2017\n
        \n
        What information we collect\n
            To use the application, you do not need to create an account.\n
            The app does not collect any personal information and does not transmit any information to other devices or services.\n
            The local store contains data related only application functionality.\n
            No information about the device is not going.\n
            The required permissions (to use the camera, record to local storage) are used to maintain the history in the app.\n
        \n
        Changes to this provision on the protection of personal data\n
        \n
            We may change this policy from time to time, and if we do we’ll post any changes in the update information in the application and the website that hosts the application. If you continue to use application after those changes are in effect, you agree to the revised policy. If the changes are significant, we may provide more prominent notice or get your consent as required by law.\n
            \n
        Contact Information\n
            Questions, suggestions, comments and reviews about the current state of the protection of personal inform at: kolosmiler@gmail.com.\n
    </string>

    <string name="help_side_panels_enable">Enable side panels</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_intro">Use side panels to keep statistics of players</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_open">Click on bottom button of left or right side panel at the main screen to open it</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_add_one">Add one player</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_add_multi">Automatically add players. (Restoring data on long press)</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_select">Select active players: click toggle button, choose players from table above and click again to apply</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_close">Close panel (also you can tap outside the panel)</string>
    <string name="help_panels_text_clear">Clear panel (shows dialog with two options: delete all players or clear points and fouls)</string>
    <string name="description_open_panel">Open panel</string>

    <string name="help_panels_text_game">
        After adding the players and choice of active players each button on the main screen will be assigned to the relevant player.\n
        When changing score or foul click on player button to apply the action to the player.\n
        Substitution active players can be either through the panel, or after long pressing on the button of the player.\n
        \n
        There is automatic data recovery players panels. Also you can do this by long pressing the button automatic adding multiple players.
    </string>

    <string name="appupdate_title">Update info</string>
    <string name="appupdate_info_link_help">help</string>
    <string name="appupdate_info">
        v.3.0:\n
          - teams profiles (see help);\n
          - restoring side panels state.\n
        v.2.7:\n
          - streetball layout and rules (settings);\n
          - custom color for shot clock;\n
          - save team names when starting a new game (done through the default in settings).\n
        v.2.6.2:\n
          - permissions requests for using camera and storage;\n
          - applying orientation preference without restarting app.\n
        v.2.6.1:\n
          - fixed some problems with camera mode;\n
          - added privacy policy;\n
          - changed horn sound.\n
        v.2.6:\n
          - technical update (contact me in case of problems);\n
          - change layout or timeout rules does not require starting new game;\n
          - custom color for main time;\n
          - application left navigation panel in camera mode.\n
        v.2.5:\n
          - updated library which caused app (v.2.4) crash;\n
          - custom colors;\n
          - fixed possession arrows state after restart or rotation.\n
        v.2.4:\n
          - save data storage format changed;\n
          - fixed setting maximum team fouls.\n
          - some other bug fixes and improvements.\n
        v.2.3:\n
          - Undo last actions and save play-by-play history.\n
        v.2.2:\n
          - portrait orientation;\n
          - possession arrows;\n
          - fix the bug of non-closing panels.\n
        v.2.1:\n
          - switch sides.\n
        v.2.0:\n
          - new help;\n
          - players panels.\n
    </string>

</resources>
